Boss,
Longqing has transferred
all the black money
to an offshore shell company,
planning to launder it
by acquiring the Wen Group.
Good.
Now that they intend to launder money,
we'll make them invest it all
in Wen Group.
Then,
they will lose everything.
You mean...
Wen Jianan,
it's time for us to work together.
These documents can prove
that the new drug is connected
to the fugitive He Mu.
So,
this drug originated from the patent
that He Mu stole from your mother,
Jiang Yuqing?
Yes.
We aren’t only here to hand
over evidence today.
He Mu owes me more than just a legal debt.
We request to join you
in hunting down He Mu.
Hunting down serious fugitives is
the police's job.
I know how you feel.
I also want to thank Miss Wen,
who collected all kinds of evidence
after the car accident.
That's how we were able to
get He Mu sentenced severely.
I also want to thank you, Mr. Jiang.
Under Representative Yin's leadership,
you cooperated with the police
to thoroughly investigate
the Qin Shan bribery case
and stopped the expansion of Qin Shan
and the evil forces behind him.
But...
Police Commissioner Chen.
Mr. Yin, why are you here?
This is the authorization document.
This case will be handled specially,
and I will personally supervise it.
Okay.
Your evidence can only prove
that He Mu is connected
to the drug ingredient,
but it can't prove
that he is directly linked to
the Wen Group’s anti-aging
beauty capsule scandal.
What do you mean?
To arrest him,
you have to complete
the chain of evidence.
Why are you getting involved in this?
[Dearest Episode 22]
Because my target
has never been He Mu.
Who is that?
Longqing.
The Longqing Gang used to
be the biggest gang in Xinggang,
committing all kinds of crimes.
Now they are making a comeback,
trying to launder their money
through He Mu
and go legitimate again.
I won't let them succeed.
Is that why you got close to me?
I got close to you
because you are interesting.
I want to help you, Wen Jianan.
Help me?
Yin Mingzhu,
don't you think that as a fan,
what you've done for me
is a bit too crazy
and too much?
Crazy?
Telling a crazy woman that she is crazy
can only give her the idea
that she can act even crazier.
And
it will make her very unhappy.
Did I make you unhappy?
Tell me.
What are your terms?
Longqing is indeed a big fish.
Catching him will also be
an achievement for me.
It's a win-win for us.
What do you plan to do?
I want you to lure Longqing into the trap
and make him invest all his black money
into Wen Group.
You want us to play along with you,
convincing him the acquisition is secure,
and then pull the ladder away
at the last step.
Once his money is
transferred domestically,
you can use your authority
to freeze his assets.
Smart girl.
You have the Wen Group
and Cloudsea's intelligence network.
And I
can bring them to justice
once and for all.
Hello?
I still have some capsules in stock.
Do you want them?
Yes.
I'll pay any price.
Kelly.
I'm here to buy drugs.
I brought a lot of money.
It's enough to buy your drugs.
Kelly.
Xin,
long time no see.
He Mu, you'd be in…
In prison?
You know,
no place can hold me.
Thanks to you,
I'll be taking over the Wen Group soon.
So, this was all your scheme.
Kelly works for you.
You told her to get close to me.
Yes.
After all these years,
you're still the most naive,
and the easiest to fool.
You've lost weight,
and look haggard.
Drug withdrawal must be tough.
Want some?
I have all the anti-aging capsules here.
As long as you cooperate with me,
I can give you
as much as you want.
Wen Xin.
Where is she?
Just this morning,
three more shareholders
withdrew their capital.
Recently, news everywhere
has been frequently reporting incidents of
side effects from the anti-aging capsules.
We've suffered heavy losses.
Ever since
the anti-aging capsule incident,
everyone has been distancing themselves
from the Wen Group.
Now even the bank is pressing us
for the loan of the Xingji theme park.
If we can't find a new capital injection,
Wen Group's cash flow won't last a month.
I'll have Hao check tomorrow
and transfer the liquid funds
from Cloudsea's account to you.
I can't use your money.
If we put all our money
in one place,
that's a real gamble.
Then what do you want to do?
We have to find someone
with enough resources,
willing to take over
at this critical moment.
I can find someone.
I know someone who can inject capital.
I've had Hao keeping an eye on Wen Xin
these past few days.
You don't need to worry
too much about her safety.
Also, I found out
that the capital behind Wen Xin
might be Longqing.
He Mu controlled Wen Xin
with drug capsules,
and made her recommend investors to you.
Having her people involved
would also make it easier
for you to accept her.
She actually...
We should have eliminated
He Mu completely back then.
Otherwise,
she wouldn't have to suffer like this.
After everything is over,
we'll send Wen Xin to rehab
and help her start over,
okay?